Welcome back. So it turns out that
مرحبًا بكم من جديد. إذن قد اتضح
the cake I made wasn't the prettiest thing in the world.
أن الكعكة التي صنعتُها ليست الأفضل ولا الأجمل على الإطلاق.
It should taste great,
يُفترض أن يكون مذاقها رائعًا؛
but it looks kind of awful.
لكنها بدت بشعة بشكلٍ ما،
Totally not something I can show up with and be proud of having at a birthday party.
وليست شيئًا يمكنني عرضه والفخر بامتلاكه في حفل عيد ميلاد على الإطلاق.
So instead of me baking the cake and frosting it,
إذن، بدلًا من أن أخبز الكعكة وأثلِّجها بنفسي،
let's just have a professional do it.
دعونا ندعُ محترفًا بهذا الأمر ليفعلها.
With this cake, I had to get all the ingredients,
في حالة هذه الكعكة، علّ أن أحضر جميع المقادير
combine them myself, watch it while it's in the oven,
وأخلطها بنفسي وأراقبها بينما هي بالفرن،
make the frosting, and then actually frost it.
وأجهِّز التثليج ثم أثلِّجها فعليًا.
I had to do everything myself.
عليّ أن أفعل كل شيء بنفسي،
It was just too much.
وهذا كان كثيرًا جدًا ببساطة.
Now, I just requested the bakery to make it for me.
الآن، طلبتُ من المخبز أن يصنعها لأجلي ببساطة.
They're working on it now and will let me know
إنهم يعملون على صنعها الآن، وسيخبرونني
when it's ready to come back and pick it up.
حين تكون جاهزة لكي تعود ونحصل على قطع منها.
So, I'm not doing all the work this time,
إذن لن أقوم بكل العمل المطلوب هذه المرة؛
but that doesn't mean it's not being done.
لكن هذا لا يعني أنني لن أنهي المهمة،
Someone there is doing all of the same steps that I did in the previous lesson.
فهناك شخص ما هناك ينفذ نفس الخطوات التي نفَّذتُها في الدرس الماضي بالكامل.
So when you use a JavaScript library like jQuery to make async requests,
إذن حين تستخدمون مكتبة JavaScript مثل jQuery لإنشاء طلبات غير متزامنة
you just request the data and then jQuery does
فإنكم تطلبون البيانات ببساطة، ومن ثم ينفذ jQuery
all of the hands-on work under the hood. Let's check it out.最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6
كل العمل التنفيذي الكامن. فلنراجع هذا.